<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title>COSCUP 2010 Speakers</title>
  <link href="http://coscup.org/2010/zh-tw/program/" />
  <updated>2010-07-30T08:08:40Z</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Kan-Ru Chen</name>
  </author>
  <id>urn:uuid:29dfa6e6-43f3-31c0-8832-94e368e00c26</id>

  <entry>
    <title>Akhil Laddha (Novell)</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:e4e78086-f56a-34d4-a5e1-ea60b3e9609e</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T11:55:02Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
      <p>
      Akhil has been working on GNOME for more than three years. His
      major contribution includes testing of evolution and GNOME wide
      bug triaging. Last year he topped the bug closer list. He was
      the top bug reporter for Q4 in last year. Last to last year, he
      was at 4th position in bug closer list. He is an active member
      of bug squad.
      </p>
      ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Xan López</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:9ad0bcaf-96be-35b8-b714-233a6ddc8af7</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T12:16:54Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
      <p>
        Xan López is a Free Software developer working in Igalia. He’s
        a GNOME contributor, maintaining the Epiphany web browser, and
        a WebKit reviewer, where he spends most of his time improving
        and extending the GTK+ port of the engine.
      </p>
      ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Yuren Ju</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:1393163a-9373-33ee-bd27-02f436e94aec</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T12:19:53Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
      <p>現實生活中叫作小朱，對開放源碼軟體社群的參與跟撰寫軟體充滿興趣。
      從南到北的生活分別參加了KaLUG與Hacking Thursday的社群活動。在與開
      放源碼社群的朋友相處時感到很歡樂。</p>
      ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>苗涛 (Tim Maio)</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:9fee83c0-254a-35a5-b182-e4e14cd6fb2c</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T12:23:43Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
      <p>working in Sun China Engineering and Research Institute on
      GNOME Accessibility testing for more than 4 years, leads
      accessibility testing for OpenSolaris/Solaris Next desktop
      products, also be responsible for 508 Assessment related works
      in Sun/Oracle desktop team. Attended the first GNOME Asia
      Summit.</p>
      ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>王珂 (Ke Wang)</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:d93d3084-7252-31dd-a3ac-c092b6324d0b</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T12:24:40Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
      <p>working in Sun China Engineering and Research Institute on
      GNOME Accessibility development. Be the author and maintainer of
      Java ATK Wrapper(an ATK implementation to help in Java
      accessibility), and have helped in many accessibility related
      bug fixing. Have also been actively involved in many other GNOME
      development.</p>
      ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Emily Chen 陳陽</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:de6d329d-2382-36bc-9cf7-f51dfd6ca336</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T12:28:28Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
      <p>Emily Chen is a software engineer working on OpenSolaris
      desktop. Now she is responsible for the quality of the Mozilla
      products like Firefox and Thunderbird on OpenSolaris. She is
      passionate about open source.  She is core contributor of
      OpenSolaris community in 2009. She worked on Google Summer of
      Code program as a mentor in 2006 and 2007. She organized the
      first ever GNOME.Asia Summit 2008 in Beijing and found the
      Beijing GNOME Users Group. She graduated from Beijing Institute
      of Technology with a masters degree in computer science. In her
      spare time, she likes snowboarding, hiking and swimming.</p>
      ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Frederic Muller (President, Software Freedom International)</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:877ddb32-a47c-3c1c-85df-859eb114f2cc</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T12:31:27Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
      <p>Frederic Muller is the President of Software Freedom
      International. He is also the founding member and former
      President of the Beijing LUG, member of China Open Source
      Promotion Union, co-organizer of many international OSS events
      in China such as Linux Developer Symposium (2008), the
      Gnome.Asia Summit, OOoCon 2008, local SFDs and blogger on ZDNet
      Asia about Linux in China, Fred is now focusing on FOSS in
      Education. The rest of the time he is assisted in his tasks at
      SFI with all the board members and of course the happy members
      of the now famous BLUG!</p>
      ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Pockey Lam (GNOME.Asia)</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:3d0a1bc8-0ef7-30ca-9f95-ae9fda1f464f</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T12:34:34Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
      <p>Pockey has been very active in promoting FOSS. She is a board
      member of GNOME.Asia, Software Freedom International,
      SFDChina.org, China OSS Promotion Union and a founding member of
      the Beijing GNOME User Group that was established not long after
      the GNOME.Asia Summit 2008. She was also the President of
      Beijing Linux User Group and has been actively contributing to a
      lot of international Free and Open Source events.</p>
      ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Holger Freyther (zecke)</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:540f0b8f-f2f4-33dc-afd7-059ec3135467</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T12:39:22Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>My name is Holger Hans Peter Freyther and I have
               been hacking on Free and OpenSource Software for the
               last decade and since about 2006 I am involved with the
               WebKit project.
               </p> ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Dave Lin (Release Engineer, Sun)</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:99f352da-f014-3a24-98f0-ffd2e9d0c916</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T12:42:15Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 I’m the release engineer in Desktop team,
                 Oracle/Sun. I’m responsible to drive the build
                 process to ensure each Desktop module is
                 built/delivered on schedule; support QA and
                 development goals; and assist in adherence to a good
                 software process(nightly builds, automation
                 testing). I also manage a lab, which has the capacity
                 of 100 workstation/servers and provides services,
                 such as auto-install/nfs/web/cvs/sunray, to over 30
                 users.
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Daiki Ueno (Red Hat i18n team)</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:19cd958c-0702-3b89-9a55-1eac5b7fc754</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T12:43:10Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 Daiki Ueno (Given Family) has been involved in free
                 software development for a dozen years. His recent
                 contributions are: Japanese SKK input-method for IBus
                 (2009), a session resuming extension for GNUTLS
                 (2009), ssh-agent support for libssh2 (2009), and
                 GNUPG interface for Emacs (2006). In April 2010 he
                 joined the Red Hat i18n team.
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Funda Wang 王鵬 (简体中文本地化 协调人)</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:d6ef5395-8f47-30c0-a87e-94c9844541db</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T12:46:25Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 Funda Wang 是简体中文本地化的协调人，领导着 GNOME、
                 KDE 等诸多翻译项目。同时，他致力于在不同的国际化项目中
                 改进中文化支持，包括输入法、字体，以及有关中文的bug修
                 复和提交。他以一个专业的国际化人士的身份，活跃于整个
                 Linux 社区。
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>黃佑仁 Rock (台大資工)</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:0f724b26-99ce-38e7-a4f8-c29ab27add79</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T12:55:21Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 台灣大學資訊工程學系大學一年級學生，2009年10月開始參與
                 自由軟體推廣活動。目前跟著台灣教育部自由軟體諮詢中心，
                 為開發＂給初學者用的自由作業系統－Ezgo＂的一份子。
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>葉志偉 (北斗國小 特教組長)</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:52bd1efb-5106-3c8d-8a33-d84385542c18</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T12:57:52Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 葉志偉，北斗國小資源班教師兼任特教組長，台灣第一本國小
                 Linux課本「Ubuntu自由學電腦」作者，深信Linux資訊教育適
                 用於國民教育階段的國中小。專門研究作業系統的輔助科技，
                 希望能將特殊教育與自由軟體結合，帶給身障者更多的支持與
                 服務。
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>FourDollars 李世元</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:ee17d8ba-71db-3dc8-a64b-8e51eaf4d780</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T13:00:25Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 四元 自由軟體與開放原始碼軟體的實習生，取之於社群，回饋於社群。
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Ping-Hsun Chen 陳品勳 penk</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:824c4f41-b0a7-3f67-b7b1-6254ec0d1fc0</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T13:03:10Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 Ping-Hsun Chen (penk) is a web and FOSS developer,
                 project leader of xPUD, enjoying in old-school rock
                 ‘n’ roll, Sci-Fi novels and volleyball, participating
                 open source related activities, writing in free
                 software, translating documents and books, loves
                 NightWish, Vonnegut and Perl.
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>劉穎駿 PaulLiu</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:ad3aa24d-4cd1-3f88-b2df-44f8f4a0c9a1</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T13:06:33Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 Debian Developer (2009~).
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Sascha Pallenberg (netbooknews.de)</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:c654b442-df13-3c0b-8c37-b181f90e7b03</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T13:11:18Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 Sascha Pallenberg has been a leading proponent of the
                 small form factor and mobile computing market for
                 several years. With the rise of the netbooks he
                 started his first mobile computing blog Eeepcnews.de
                 back in December 2007, while he was still living in
                 the US. After just 2 months he quit his job at his US
                 startup and relocated to Taipei/Taiwan to cover the
                 recent netbook news directly from its’
                 source. Netbooknews.de became a leading source for
                 all the netbook related news, even though he is still
                 blogging in German. Together with Nicole Scott he
                 founded Netbooknews.com in June 2009 to publish daily
                 mobile computing videos. In just 6 months it became
                 the most viewed reporter channel on Youtube for
                 Taiwan and one of the global Top 100 reporter
                 channels.
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>沈聖博 shengpo (Openlab.Taipei)</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:78a86e78-e830-30be-bbff-728296a25b87</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T13:13:59Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 1980年生，新生代數位藝術家。認為生活本身即是藝術，而人
                 與人之間的許多活動是生活的成份，這是最原型的互動形態，
                 你我之間一定存在著至少一種互動媒介將你我連結起來。因
                 此，擅於觀察並找出你我之間的隱性連結，並透過作品加以呈
                 現。
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>甘泰瑋</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:6e2d0ad7-863e-3a09-9ae4-cdb49003a64e</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T13:16:45Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 甘泰瑋目前就讀於元智大學資訊傳播學系碩士班互動科技組。
                 其研究興趣廣泛，主要致力於擴增實境(AR)、互動界面與情境
                 感知(Context-awareness)相關議題之研究。擴增實境研究成
                 果曾於數個虛擬實境相關國際研討會中獲得認同，部分研究成
                 果更獲今年ACM SIGGRAPH評審青睞，暑假將赴洛杉磯以
                 Poster形式發表。在互動裝置創作方面，今年(2010)有兩樣作
                 品於ACM SIGGRAPH SPACETIME互動競賽中獲入圍，並將在洛杉
                 磯展出。而過去的創作也曾被404國際電子藝術節與國內創作
                 競賽中被認同，情境感知運算相關創作方面則於ISEA國際電子
                 藝術研討會與國內研討會中獲得認同。在研究與創作的過程
                 中，常常會運用到FLOSS開放原始碼軟體，如Pure Data,
                 Processing, ARToolKit, Arduino等。因此在研究所就讀期
                 間，累積了不少使用經驗與心得可與同好分享，目前已有部分
                 心得與教學於個人部落格中與網友分享。
               </p>
               <p>
                 今年九月將赴台灣大學資訊網路與多媒體研究所攻讀博士學
                 位，未來將以行動裝置的情境感知與適地性服務之設計為研究
                 與創作方向，也期許自己能持續的在學術或創作上付出更多心
                 力，並將所學回饋社會。
               </p>
               <p>個人網站 http://www.twkan.com</p>
               <p>部落格 http://jwill.pixnet.net</p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>張正一 魔法設計師</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:6ecebfae-efa2-3b56-9e41-535fa7b98e17</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T13:19:33Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 自由軟體工作者-libdgg動態組字引擎開發、MonkeyGTK中譯版
                 等FLOSS+art音樂創作人兼推廣者，現為Openlab.Taipei的ㄧ
                 員
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Christopher Adams (Sharism.org)</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:63199374-4756-321f-9a6b-8848f9a986e3</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T13:21:03Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 Christopher Adams is a publishing professional and
                 free culture advocate. Freesouls: captured and
                 released by Joi Ito was his first Creative
                 Commons-licensed publishing project. Christopher is a
                 founding member of Sharism.org, and a member of the
                 Creative Commons Network.
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Ike Panhc (Canonical)</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:5c43e86e-fdc2-388b-a39e-3f8a59166be0</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T13:07:48Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 Ike Panhc, works in Hardware Enablement Team at
                 Canonical. Canonical is the number-one provider of
                 Ubuntu services.
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>林誠夏 (專案經理, 中央研究院)</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:36e09121-92f9-30ca-b211-c69a0806e764</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T13:23:48Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 林誠夏 (Lucien Lin) ，網路暱稱為 『Lucien』 或
                 『lucien.cc』，知識背景是科技法律，但是也喜歡了解任何
                 新奇有趣的東西。於2005年開始專職研究自由軟體授權條款，
                 專長在於自由軟體授權條款的解說分析，以及自由軟體商業運
                 用模式的觀察記錄。目前任職於中央研究院自由軟體鑄造場，
                 兼任專案經理與法政研究，同時亦負責自由軟體鑄造場電子報
                 的編輯工作。更多的活動參與及工作記錄請參閱OSSF Who’s
                 Who的個人資料
                 表
                 ：http://whoswho.openfoundry.org/people/userprofile/lucien.html
                 。
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Harald Welte (gpl-violations.org)</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:a4483bf9-0ad8-3d7f-a78b-319ef2f7c607</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T13:25:33Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 Harald Welte is a Free Software developer involved
                 with many projects from the Linux Kernel to Openmoko
                 as well as various GSM and RFID related projects. In
                 2004 he has started the gpl-violations.org project
                 which has enforced more than 150 cases of GPL license
                 infringements till today.
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Shane Coughlan (Open Invention Network)</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:74c1452e-d192-3428-921c-286d1c6ddeff</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T13:26:52Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 Shane Coughlan is an expert in communication methods
                 and business development. He is best known for
                 building bridges between commercial and
                 non-commercial stakeholders in the technology
                 sector. His professional accomplishments include
                 establishing a legal department for the main NGO
                 promoting Free Software in Europe, building a
                 professional network of over 200 legal counsel and
                 technical experts across 27 countries, and aligning
                 corporate and community interests to launch the first
                 law review dedicated to Free/Open Source Software.
               </p>
               <p>
                 Shane has extensive knowledge of Internet
                 technologies, management best practice, community
                 building and Free/Open Source Software. His
                 experience includes engagement with the server,
                 desktop, embedded and mobile telecommunication
                 industries. He does business in Europe, Asia and the
                 Americas, and maintains a broad network of contacts.
               </p>
                 ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Soeren Rabenstein (ASUSTeK Computer Inc.)</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:708b6eb8-7a8d-3a0f-b41e-ed6169c293e7</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T13:32:44Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 Education
- Second German State Exam in Law (bar admission, eligibility as judge), Berlin, focus: International Private Law
- Master of Laws, University of Cape Town, research focus: Information Technology Law, International Trade Law
- First German State Exam in Law, FU and HU Berlin, study focus: Commercial Law, Intellectual Property Law

Work Experience
- Corporate Counsel Legal Compliance (European Law and Free Open Source Licenses) at ASUSTeK Computer Inc., Taiwan
- Interim Manager of Operations at Behringer Holdings Pte. Limited, Singapore
- Project Counsel e-commerce at Payment Processing Corporation, Philippines
- Barrister pupillage at Berlin High Court, Germany
- Lecturer on Media Convergence topics at Graduate School of Business, University of Cape Town, South Africa
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>翁千婷 whiteg (中研院 研究助理)</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:875a121a-dd9e-3f80-953f-18a05c8b44c4</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T13:34:58Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 Currently a research assistant in IIS,
                 Sinica. Interested in human-computer interaction and
                 F/OSS.
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Tony Chan (Developer Advocate, Google)</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:9a09d92f-ea7d-3558-9907-921a888c0654</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T13:36:37Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 Tony Chan joined Google in 2007 as a developer
                 program engineer.  Since then, he helped developers
                 with various Google products/APIs like Google
                 Checkout, Apps and Android. Currently, Tony is a
                 developer advocate for Android. Prior joining Google,
                 Tony was a senior application developer at the
                 University of Michigan and a management consultant at
                 PricewaterhouseCooper. He received his M.B.A and
                 M.S.E. degrees from University of Michigan, Ann
                 Arbor.
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Allan Patrick D. Caeg (Philippine Open Source Network Inc.)</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:463382f1-7df1-3f74-b498-12516f11024d</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T13:38:09Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 I am a User Experience professional who learned about
                 this field by contributing to Open Source design. I
                 contribute mostly to Ubuntu and GNOME. My FOSS
                 advocacy includes my being a board member of the
                 Philippine Open Source Network, being a Coordinator
                 of Mozilla Philippines Community, and my enthusiasm
                 for Android. I design for web, desktop, and mobile
                 platforms. You can find more information about me
                 here http://live.gnome.org/AllanCaeg
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Tim Yang (Product Manager, Linpus)</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:fbe71d5f-e36f-3820-a700-0211655e6464</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T13:43:07Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 Tim Yang got his B.E. from University of Science and
                 Technologies of China and MSC from University of
                 Western Ontario, Canada, both in Computer Science. He
                 holds a position as product manager in Linpus
                 Technologies Inc starting from Apr. 2009. In Linpus,
                 he is in charge of the product design for Linpus
                 Linux Lite series. Prior to join Linpus, he worked in
                 HP for three years as a project manager.
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>黃志偉 cwhuang</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:6c8cc760-41dc-3443-aa70-0b6516d38e43</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T13:44:38Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 講者參與開放源碼運動已有超過十年的時間。發起或主持過
                 CLE、CLDP、Android-x86 等計劃，並參與 GNU Gatekeeper、
                 OpenH323、Asterisk、KDE、GNOME 等開發工作。
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>黃敬群 jserv (0xlab)</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:a0ff19fb-c417-37d3-9e92-604636fa02d9</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T13:46:08Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 0xlab developer
               </p>
               <p>blog (0xlab): http://jserv.blogspot.com/</p>
               <p>blog: http://blog.linux.org.tw/jserv/</p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>劉昱賢 thomasysliu</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:d972f8b7-c298-374c-8332-fd4e65d9d1a6</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T13:47:48Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 交通大學電子工程系學生，對嵌入式系統領域稍有涉獵。
                 Thomas 之前於晶心科技，一間台灣 32 位元處理器的 IC 設
                 計公司打工。在台灣心的開發平台，都靠 Game Emulator 騙
                 吃騙喝。近年來由於工作與興趣關係研究 Game Emulator，熱
                 於探索應用自由軟體的應用模式與機會。
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>林弘德 piaip (Google Chrome OS team)</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:b1967748-5d9e-35b9-91dc-d900d02b782a</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T13:49:36Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 * current member of the Google Chrome OS team
               </p>
               <p>* skilled in reverse engineering and tamper resistance technology</p>
               <p>
                 * participated in open source projects such as Mozilla, VIM, PuTTY, PTTBBS
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>詹宗翰 (Product Manager, Nokia )</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:d6bb5ec0-dad8-3409-8e14-a78becd614f7</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T13:51:36Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 Nokia Product Manager
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>朱立 walkingice (0xlab)</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:2f4208ca-2108-3979-a27c-e29ef33a76e7</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T13:53:06Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 0xlab developer,
                 blog: http://walkingice.twbbs.org/blog
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>林智斌 Macpaul</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:98030920-a637-34f8-9be9-11bb49149425</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T13:54:27Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 Macpaul，喜歡亂入，愛管閒事的人。對環保、非主流議題有
                 興趣。在學校裡頭學網通領域出身，曾經在台灣的網通系統整
                 合廠服務過。現在在產業鍊的最上游服務，希望藉由這種機
                 會，來把產業升級的理念，落實到產業鍊之中。
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>唐鳳</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:3c30078c-513e-3a45-a65d-f363d0d02644</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T13:57:03Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 唐鳳。真核域。動物界。脊索動物門。脊椎動物亞門。哺乳綱。
                 靈長目。人科。人屬。智人。（啊，你也是？真巧！） (
                 註：據維基百科描述，唐鳳是 Pugs 專案的發起人，領導
                 Haskell 和 Perl 社群協力開發 Perl 6 語言。唐鳳也致力於
                 自由軟體的國際化工作，包括設計 Kwiki、RT 及 Slash 等系
                 統的國際化架構，並發起多項開放源碼書籍的翻譯計劃。在
                 CPAN 上，唐鳳負責維護 100 餘項的 Perl 相關專案，包括
                 Perl Archive Toolkit (PAR) 這項跨平台封裝及建置工具，
                 以及 CPAN 的自動測試及數位簽署系統等。)
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>畢瑄易 ericpi (資深工程師, KKBOX)</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:2b553e5e-af20-39b1-9bb9-4fb73e31fed1</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T13:58:27Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 曾任北京天玩科技技術經理, 目前於願境網訊股份有限公司
                 (KKBOX)的研發中心擔任資深工程師, 主要負責 KKBOX 後端系
                 統平台相關的設計開發工作; 喜愛各種 Open Source 應用,
                 為 Gentoo、FreeBSD 愛好者.
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Eric Bidelman (Developer Advocate, Google)</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:9fc0a263-281d-3106-8e33-de1c8a4b8c41</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T13:59:54Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 Eric is an engineer and developer advocate on
                 Google’s Developer Relations team. Over the last two
                 years he’s worked on various developers focused
                 products, including Google Docs, Sites, Health, and
                 OAuth. Recently, Eric joined the Chrome team to help
                 spread HTML5 goodness around the globe. Prior to
                 Google, Eric worked as a software engineer at the
                 University of Michigan where he designed rich web
                 applications and APIs for the university’s 19
                 libraries. Eric holds a B.S.E in Computer Engineering
                 and a B.S.E in Electrical Engineering from the
                 University of Michigan, Ann Arbor.
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>陳官辰 freedom (工研院)</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:2d65b838-3906-3ce0-bc17-16c59a02d78c</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T14:02:45Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 Koan-Sin Tan is a veteran open source / unix user. He
                 learnt to use simple Basic programs on Multitech
                 MPF-II (宏碁 小教授二號) in early 1980s, then learnt
                 to use and write code for Unix on a VAX-11/780
                 running 4.3BSD in late 1980s.
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>蔣定宇 josephj (專案副理, D-Link)</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:52587fee-e935-393a-8da3-304db0927d2f</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T14:05:28Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 蔣定宇，網路代號 josephj，對於新技術跟程式碼有著強烈的
                 偏執狂：開發注重 Semantic、Maintenance、Accessibility、
                 Usability。目前任職於 D-Link 友訊科技擔任專案副理，利
                 用 YUI 3 OOP 的概念製作跨網站的服務。
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>尤孝庭 笨笨的小B (Mozilla Jetpack 大使)</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:cc191c4e-c6cb-390b-a31c-41594bfd122d</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T14:06:48Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 尤孝庭（笨笨的小B），Mozilla 官方指派之 Jetpack 大使。阿宅一枚。台灣大學電機工程學系學生、MozTW志工、長年專研 Web Programming 領域。
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Michael(tm) Smith (HTML Activity/WG lead, W3C)</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:20e2076b-fb61-3ba8-b82a-41b17fb2894c</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T14:08:24Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 Mike Smith is the HTML Activity/WG lead of W3C and
                 also an active player of WHATWG, the group that
                 started the HTML5. He now mediates between people who
                 have issues around HTML5. He is also a main developer
                 of validator.vu, an HTML5 validator which is now
                 being integrated into the famous W3C validator.
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>謝子斌 (Web Evangelist, Opera)</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:eefb14ed-3d6d-3f8c-ab1b-f6c0fde558df</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T14:09:56Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 謝子斌從事網路標準研究，現任挪威 Opera 軟件公司網路標
                 準專（Web Evangelist），其工作包括了推廣 HTML5 和
                 CSS3 的發展。除了在台灣 PC ADV／電腦王雜誌有專欄文章發
                 表之外，今年也會在北京 W3C Day 演講。
                 (http://webrebuild.org/y/beijing/2 /)。他預測德國今年
                 會贏得世界杯，如果沒有你可以在會場和他要一件 Opera
                 t-shirt。Twitter：zibin
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>胡崇偉 Marr (中研院 研究助理)</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:f3328aa1-91f3-3b5c-93e4-bf2ee48ddbeb</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T14:11:38Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 Marr 是 Python 程式語言愛好者，在中央研究院資訊科學研
                 究所擔任研究助理，參與 Open Source Software Foundry 的
                 營運工作。同時也是軟體自由協會理監事。平常參與技術文件
                 撰寫，任何關於 Python 的話題都有興趣外，也投注 Linux
                 系統整合、程式人員生產力的議題。
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>郭文傑 (國網中心)</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:34197b0c-177c-3bfc-9b0d-641464cdf48f</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T14:13:17Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 nchc 自由軟體實驗室
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Shih-Yong Wang (Software Engineer, Yahoo! Taiwan)</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:96d10f81-58a7-3c14-a4ac-9a37001b9b16</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T14:14:30Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 Software engineer, Yahoo! Taiwan
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Michael Pan (CEO, nephosity)</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:919d2e1c-4ae3-3dc8-a694-5656ba560c3e</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T14:16:52Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 Michael Pan is the CEO and founder of nephosity. He
                 has over 10years working on high performance
                 (distributed, grid, cloud) computing. in a previous
                 life, he has worked at DreamWorks animation, NIH
                 Center for Computational Biology, JPL, and HPLabs.
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>翟本喬 (台達電子 資深處長)</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:e351d212-5e47-32dc-8d68-7e99d9284d75</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T14:19:59Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 翟本喬博士畢業於紐約大學電腦科學系，2003 年進入
                 Google 主持伺服器平台之規劃，共設計四代之伺服器以及其
                 他多項硬體，Google 之高效率單電壓電源供應器設計即出自
                 其手，貨櫃型資料中心及內建電池之伺服器亦是由其團隊所設
                 計，2007-2009 在 Google 台北工程中心主持軟體研發計劃，
                 2009-2010 回到美國 Google 進行資料中心之研發。2010 年
                 4 月回到台灣加入台達電子，擔任雲端技術中心資深處長，負
                 責有關雲端運算硬體及軟體之整合與開發。
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>高嘉璘 AceLan (Kernel Engineer, Canonical )</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:c03615db-c269-381e-8282-1fd3eaa3aec4</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T14:25:09Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 Canonical kernel engineer，曾任 KDE@Taiwan
                 coordinator，及參與 {linux,debian}.org.tw 各項事務
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>吳政璋 小璋丸</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:e79e51ef-a7b6-37ea-a816-0e1653292346</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T14:26:52Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 我是個小小的程序員
喜歡用 Open Source 的資源來完成自己的工作
此外自己也正在研發一些屬於自己的好玩事物
關於我的作品可以參考
               </p>
               <p>
http://code.google.com/p/uvajava
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>李圭峰 Thinker</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:316763ee-dd58-3b47-afca-22aba6ef37c2</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T14:28:10Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 開發了 MadButterfly，ajaxmind，netgraffiti 等專案，您
                 可以在這裡找到他的心得
                 http://heaven.branda.to/~thinker/GinGin_CGI.py
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>許洛豪 Brian Hsu</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:1fa871ef-a3f4-3db3-b64d-b89059539ab2</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T14:30:51Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 Brian Hsu（墳墓）只是個萌程式、動畫、漫畫、遊戲和輕小說的阿宅。
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>宗豪 tsung</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:13c54ec2-8257-3342-a73b-a75bebec6b2c</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T14:32:25Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 Tsung 是個於網路業界四處遊走的平凡人
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>楊士青 依瑪貓 (昇陽教育中心講師)</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:a7f1434b-bf0d-3f65-9404-66aa0ae4ccf9</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T14:29:37Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 依瑪貓╱楊士青，曾任OpenOffice.org 應用開發工程師，目前
                 擔任昇陽電腦教育訓練中心專任講師，資策會教育訓練中心兼
                 任講師等，並於最近加入 Debian 的 OpenOffice.org 套件團
                 隊。並擅長 Perl/PHP 程式語言與網站系統開發，為資深的
                 Perl 燒機測試人員，MySQL AB Basic Quality Contributer。
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>周立瑋 sleepnova</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:d9486578-c0c1-3c44-889b-161ed8ddba0b</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T14:23:03Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 擁有數學魂的資訊人，致力於尋找更佳的程式設計典範。嚴重
                 精神潔癖，不能忍受程式碼裡頭有不乾淨的東西。反省資訊人
                 的社會責任，資訊人除了自我感覺良好之外，還能為社會做點
                 什麼?目前身份為資訊浪人，過著周遊列國的日子，四海為家…
                 (Android 呼叫小黃 及 Chrome 小字典 作者)
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>彭兆蔚 / ply (資策會 專案經理)</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:bc2436f7-0b92-3692-9fdc-d044167f6595</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T14:21:19Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 台大資工所畢業，曾任台大資訊系統訓練班 Java 課程與
                 Ajax 課程講師，現於資策會擔任專案經理與軟體工程師職務。
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Gasol (PIXNET)</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:b4a23bd4-072b-31b3-910e-90562c2fab72</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T14:18:45Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Tick Chen</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:e88adeea-2cde-3a48-9e86-934ea67a63c5</id>
    <updated>2010-07-30T08:59:20Z</updated>
    <summary>
      0xlab developer
      blog: http://linuxocarina.blogspot.com/
    </summary>
  </entry>

  <entry>
    <title>Matt Hsu</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:fa7b0d23-124a-31cf-aad7-fe6bef703843</id>
    <updated>2010-07-30T09:00:39Z</updated>
    <summary>
      0xlab developer
      blog: http://matthsu-abacus.blogspot.com/
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Charles McCathieNevile (Chief Standards Officer, Opera)</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:df7a672b-14b3-334d-9c22-8896c399f66e</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T14:35:09Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 Charles McCathieNevile 自 2005 年起於Opera Software擔
                 任首席網路標準長(Chief Standards Officer)。加入Opera
                 之前，他曾於全球資訊網協會（World Wide Web
                 Consortium，簡稱W3C）工作，參與制定大部份核心的網路標
                 準如HTML、CSS、SVG與其他開放性標準技術等。他現在代表
                 Opera在W3C的網路應用小組擔任共同主持人，並且是W3C諮詢
                 委員會一員。同時，Charles 在國際上是公認知名的無障礙網
                 頁 (Web Accessibility) 專家，在網際網路方面涉略廣泛，
                 包括網際網路的社會層面、如何幫助開發者更簡易有效地創造
                 網頁內容與應用，適合給所有人、所有裝置上存取。
                 Charles 是澳洲人，在學時修習西洋中古世紀歷史並取得學
                 位，目前在西班牙與挪威之間兩地工作。
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>Brian Cameron</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:96e5e9fb-a1ac-3976-9c5b-3c3e024b2409</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T14:36:41Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 Brian Cameron is a free software advocate and has
                 worked for the past 10 years as a senior engineer on
                 the GNOME Desktop at Sun Microsystems and now
                 Oracle. Brian has served on the GNOME Foundation
                 board of directors for the past 2.5 years and is
                 currently acting as secretary. Brian has also been
                 the maintainer of GDM since January, 1995.
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>张弛</title>
    <id>urn:uuid:23835a3a-be5c-3a5e-a75d-911cbda0ebda</id>
    <updated>2010-08-13T14:38:20Z</updated>
    <summary>
      <![CDATA[
               <p>
                 张弛先生现任Nokia, Qt开发框架大中国地区技术经理，负责
                 战略客户以及合作伙伴的技术咨询和业务拓展等工作。并在商
                 业客户，开源社区和大学中积极推广Qt技术。此前，他一直任
                 职于奇趣科技（ Qt公司前身 ）和摩托罗拉公司，在移动通讯
                 领域有着丰富的知识和经验。 张弛是公认的Qt专家，在许多
                 公开会议中发表演讲。对移动生态系统，包括手机及消费电
                 子，中间件以及第三方应用，有着丰富的经验。
               </p>
               ]]>
    </summary>
  </entry>
</feed>
